# Chin Bing Hong

www.linkedin.com/in/chin-bing-hong/ | https://binglebangle-bh.github.io/

Probing, poking, and pestering the cyber security elements of each application seems to be my forte. While cyber security has always been my expertise, I enjoy building and developing blockchain elements as well!

### Activity

Hackathon: Solana Builders League 2023 Year 2023

3<sup>rd</sup> Place

Hackathon: GovTech Jaga the Stack(Stack the code)

Year 2022

2<sup>nd</sup> Place (Open Category)

Polkadot Hackathon: North America Edition 2022 Year 2022

1<sup>st</sup> Place (DeFi Category)

Cyber Defenders Discovery Camp (CTF)
Year 2020

**Participant** 

# Relevant Working Experience

Pulsesecure Pte Ltd, Singapore

Jan 2022 - Present

### **Associate Consultant (Penetration Tester)**

- Web application testing | Mobile application testing | Host Audit | Vulnerability Assessment | API testing
- Done over 50+ Projects and counting

#### Cyber Security Agency of Singapore, CSA

### **Singapore Computer Emergency Response Team**

Jun 2020 - Aug 2020

- Actualize ransomware prevention materials to target 40% of Singapore organization that got hit by ransomware to 0%
- Work closely with upper management to produce a prevention material targeting all local businesses

# Singapore Armed Force, Army CIO Office

Jun 2018 - Aug 2019

## **Network Specialist**

- Monitor organization's networks for security breaches to maintain 0% security breach
- Plan a mass computer upgrades for the entire army and presented to a hall of over 100+ individuals

# Skills & Certification

Language Certification

English, Chinese(Mandarin) OSWE, OSCE, OSCP, CEHv10

Tech Language Tech Tools

Python, Rust, Solidity Git, Docker, Prometheus, Ethereum, Solana, Grafana

### Education

### Singapore Institute of Technology

Sep 2019 - Jan 2023

BEng (Hons) ICT (Information Security)

Honours with Distinction